chinadiscovery.com 2012-10-24

# Privacy and Security Policy

www.chinadiscovery.com  is aware that the security of your private information from the use of our website is an important concern. We take the protection of your personal information very seriously. Therefore we would like you to know what information we maintain and what information we discard. With this privacy notice, we would like to inform you about our security measures.

**Collection and processing of personal data**  
We collect personal information only when you provide it to us, through registration, completion of forms or e-mails, as part of an order for travel service and tour requests and similar situations in which you have chosen to provide the information to us. Your personal information will not be passed on by us for use by third parties in any form whatsoever, unless we have obtained your consent or are legally required to do so. We will retain control of and responsibility for the use of any personal information you disclose to us. 

**What kinds of information we collect from you?**

•Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, nationality, phone number, zip code

•Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address

•Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number

•Passport and Visa data

•Your interests and special requests for your food, accommodation, etc. in your trip.

**Purposes of Use**  
The information we collect will only be used for the purpose of supplying you with the requested tours or services or for other purposes for which you have given your consent, except where otherwise provided by law.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To design a tailor-made trip to your best interests  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs while customizing your tour.

• To obtain airline tickets and hotel bookings & to apply for travel permits in certain regions in China (Tibet)

• To improve our website   
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

• To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

• To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent. 

• To send newsletters as your request   
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you our latest newsletters about travel news, updated tours, or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future newsletters, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  
 **Choice and Opt-Out  
** If you no longer wish to receive our Newsletters, you may "opt-out" of receiving them by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in the each newsletter that we sent or you can contact us at  info@chinadiscovery.com
